A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 5: Negatives, 1980-1986
  - Giant Food, NOVA, TSC, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - James Micklewright, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - Joseph Flakne, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - William Burkholder, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - EQUAC, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - Mayor Barry, Lorton Contract, 1985 June 10 (Box 9)
  - TRW John Cook, 1985 June 12 (Box 9)
  - James Cox - Fairfax-Falls Church Community Services Board, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Child Safety Day - Paula Shea, Joyce Schultz, Pat Smith, Billy Bob Hoskins, Bob Daski, Eileen McGovern, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Eliece Altroggen, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Eric Schwalber - 1985 Presidential Scholar, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Howard Simpson, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Jane Deppler - Shelter House, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Sandy and Herb Aman - Fairfax Symphony, 1985 June 17 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Fair, 1985 July (Box 9)
  - Dorothy Irvin, 1985 July 8 (Box 9)
  - Jack Chilton, 1985 July 8 (Box 9)
  - Carmin Caputo, 1985 July 8 (Box 9)
  - James Kitchin, 1985 July 8 (Box 9)
  - Sid Steele, portraits, 1985 July 8 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's Office, 83 year old man high school diploma, 1985 July 19 (Box 9)
  - North County Governmental Center, 1985 July 22 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector bus with Supervisors Alexander, Egge, McConnell, 1985 July 22 (Box 9)
  - 1985 NACo Awards, 1985 July 22 (Box 9)
  - Private Industry Council Retirees, 1985 July 22 (Box 9)
  - Bradford Dempsey - Cent. Of A. for Work on Trees, 1985 July 22 (Box 9)
  - Barbara Fried, 1985 July 29 (Box 9)
  - Jacquelline Cobb, 1985 July 29 (Box 9)
  - Fire Fighters Muscular Dystrophy Week, 1985 July 29 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Fair Contributors, 1985 July 29 (Box 9)
  - Mary Markham and M. Kendrick, 1985 July 29 (Box 9)
  - Herbert Eaker, 1985 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Paul Arnone, 1985 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Judith Garcia, 1985 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Emilie Miller, 1985 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Certificates of Appreciation - Kevin Bell, Col. John E. Granfield, Dr. Robert R. Spillane, Thomas M. Stevens, Daniel Lanier, James A. Thur, Frances Tyahla, Louis L. Herzog, Thomas N. Young, 1985 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector Bus and Egge, 1985 August 23 (Box 9)
  - Anita Ruggles, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - Northern Virginia Community Collect - Dr. Richard J. Ernst, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - Robert Bodine, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - West Potomac High School Drill Team, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - American Heart Food Festival, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - Voter Registration Month - Charlene Ruden, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - PANDAA, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - MADD - Lou Herzog, 1985 September 9 (Box 9)
  - DAR Constitution Week, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Mary Grace Lintz, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - United Way Month, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Carl Coan, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - John Fletcher, Frank Quinn Jr., 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Emergency Medical Services Week - Doug Casey, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Board Room - African Ethiopian relief Children to Children, 1985 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's office - Cross Country handicapp, 1985 September 20 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector commuter bus ribboncutting, 1985 September 28 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector commuter bus ribboncutting - Dana Kaufman, 1985 September 28 (Box 9)
  - Down Syndrome Month, 1985 October 7 (Box 9)
  - National Resources Conservation Week - Richard Terwilliger, Robert Doyle, Norman Jeffries, Gloria Fisher, 1985 October 7 (Box 9)
  - Hunger Awareness Week - Rev. Sherwood McCay, John Pender, Herb Brynildsen, Mrs. Sidoux Mitchell, 1985 October 7 (Box 9)
  - Fire Prevention Week - Warren E. Isman, Freeland Young, William Burris, 1985 October 7 (Box 9)
  - Financial Reporting Award - Warren S. Hutchinson, 1985 October 7 (Box 9)
  - Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Week (SIDS), 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Joan Dumas, Library Board of Trustees, 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Miss Wheelchair Virginia - Judy Munske, 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Michael Gick, 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Business and Professional Women's Week - Sheila Barry and Nancy Stacy, 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Comm. for Handicapp - Steve Hall, West Park, Rights of Persons - Rosen, 1985 October 21 (Box 9)
  - Korean Officials Briefing - Judges Dining Room, 1985 October 22 (Box 9)
  - Springfield Road Improvement - Amherst Avenue extension, 1985 October 26 (Box 9)
  - Amherst Avenue Bridge, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - John Ferguson family, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Nancy Camaur - Library Board of Trustees, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Helen Wilson - group and Joe Alexander, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Substance Abuse Week - Harriet Ball, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Youth Appreciation Week, Northern Virginia Optimists Clubs, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Hospice Month, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Reston 72 Hour House Project, 1985 October 28 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's Office - Epilepsy Month, 1985 November 7 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's Office - Washington Dulles Task Force, 1985 November 8 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's Office - Mrs. Witt presents book "History of Northern Virginia", 1985 November 15 (Box 9)
  - Janew Vitray, Commission for Women, 1985 November 18 (Box 9)
  - Virginia State Police, VDH&T Hot-line, Captain H.D. Northern, David Gehr, 1985 November 18 (Box 9)
  - Lazy Daisies Homemakers Club "Please Call Police" signs, 1985 November 18 (Box 9)
  - Firefighters Canteen - C. David Litzenburg, Joe McManus, Buddy Behringer of Southland Corporation, 1985 November 25 (Box 9)
  - School Buses, 1985 December 2 (Box 9)
  - Herrity's Office - Pearl Harbor Day, 1985 December 4 (Box 9)
  - International Children's Festival, 1985 December 9 (Box 9)
  - Temporaries, Inc., 1985 December 9 (Box 9)
  - Fall Bond Referendum - Citizens Task Force, 1985 December 9 (Box 9)
  - Coalition for Balance Transportation, 1985 December 9 (Box 9)
  - Northern Virginia Patriots drum corps - Sam and Nanette Evans, 1985 December 16 (Box 9)
  - Northern Virginia Refugee Community - Statue of Liberty, 1985 December 16 (Box 9)
  - Volunteer Firefighters of the Year Awards - C. David Litzenburg, Edgar Cobb, Michael Zucker, Gerry Morganthal, Fred Keck, 1985 December 16 (Box 9)
  - Samuel Patteson, Supervisor of Assessments, 1986 January 6 (Box 9)
  - Seats Belts in School Buses, 1986 January 6 (Box 9)
  - Monsignor Thomas P. Scannell, St. Michael's Catholic Church, 1986 January 27 (Box 9)
  - James Payne, 1986 January 27 (Box 9)
  - Kathleen Smith, CPR, 1986 January 27 (Box 9)
  - Children's Dental Month - Dr. Scott Leaf, D.D.S., Northern Virginia Dental Society, 1986 February 10 (Box 9)
  - Vocational Education Week - Dr. Robert Spillane, 1986 February 10 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Junior Miss Contest - Lori Jo Smith, 1986 February 10 (Box 9)
  - Big Brother Organization - Herrity's office, 1986 February 21 (Box 9)
  - Northern Virginia Community College Appreciation plaque, 1986 February 24 (Box 9)
  - Dietetic Month - Herrity's Office [Gloria Sealy, Am. Dietetic], 1986 February 28 (Box 9)
  - ECHO - Albert Dwoskin and Edwin Lynch, 1986 March 10 (Box 9)
  - Rotterdam, Netherlands Fire Department - Willem van Arenthals and Joop Kowlmans, 1986 March 10 (Box 9)
  - YMCA Week - Herrity's Office (Doth eyes closed), 1986 March 14 (Box 9)
  - Child Care Provides portraits - Donna Kesler, Alyce Chessnoe, Madeline Fried, Frances Pamico, 1986 March 20 (Box 9)
  - Andrew L. Daniels, Public Works retiree, 1986 March 24 (Box 9)
  - June Y. Attmanspacher, Circuit Court retiree, 1986 March 24 (Box 9)
  - Lou Rubenstein, World Health - Herrity's Office, 1986 March 26 (Box 9)
  - Mo. Schulding, J.E.B. Stuart 10K Race - Herrity's Office, 1986 March 26 (Box 9)
  - Print Shop cake, 1986 March 27 (Box 9)
  - Heart Fund Raiser - J. Lambert jailed, 1986 April 1 (Box 9)
  - Week of the Young Child - Judith Beattie, Lynda O'Bryan, Virginia Holton, Alyce Chessno, 1986 April 7 (Box 9)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month - Linda Hossenlopp, 1986 April 7 (Box 9)
  - Victims Rights Week - Lou Herzog, 1986 April 7 (Box 9)
  - Fair Housing Month - Jon Strother, 1986 April 7 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector sign kiosk, 1986 April 11 (Box 9)
  - Commission for Women - Audrey Markham, 1986 April 16 (Box 9)
  - Commission for Women - Lossie Tucker, 1986 April 16 (Box 9)
  - Commission for Women - Mary Roots, 1986 April 16 (Box 9)
  - Commission for Women - Gladys Busbrol, 1986 April 16 (Box 9)
  - Commission for Women - Victoria Nehlig, 1986 April 16 (Box 9)
  - Volunteer Action Center - Herrity's Office, 1986 April 17 (Box 9)
  - Arbor Day, 1986 April 28 (Box 9)
  - Service Extraordinaire - Herrity's Office [Melody Smith], 1986 April 30 (Box 9)
  - High's Stores - Herrity's Office, 1986 May 2 (Box 9)
  - Older Americans Month - Catherine Brooks, James Reilly, 1986 May 5 (Box 9)
  - Small Business Week - Karl Nelson, Linda Wright, Caroline Schlipf, Dale Peck, 1986 May 5 (Box 9)
  - Historic Preservation Week - Mary Fahringer (Fairfax County History Commission), 1986 May 5 (Box 9)
  - Mental Health Month - Richard Rosenfield, Elizabeth Lee McManus, 1986 May 5 (Box 9)
  - Peoples Drug, Drug Fair, Adult Magazine - Herrity's Office, 1986 May 6 (Box 9)
  - Insurance Women of Northern Virginia, Brian's certificate Brady - Herrity's Office, 1986 May 13 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Clothing Resource Center, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Tourism Week - James P. Popino, James N. Larsen, James Wordsworth, John Lynch, Thomas G. Morr, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Public Works Week - Mary Jacobs, Roxanne Tomlinson, Tom Dorman, Jimmy Jones, Frank Murphy, Mohammed Gharavi, Mary Carroll, Brian Earhart, Dan Mobley, Dynita Glenn, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - 1986 Savings Bond Campaign - Jane Copeland, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Warren Hutchison, Financial Reporting, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - EQUAC Intern Jenniford Rexford, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Press Room, Press in Board Room for Fairfax Fair, 1986 May 19 (Box 9)
  - Onthank Awards, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Retirees of 30 Years - Wallace Robertson, Hugh Murtagh, Phillip G. Robertson, Catherine D. Wood, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax County Adult Softball Council - Bill Austin, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - "Take On A Killer" Time - AMC Cancer Research Center, Lynn Dangelmaier, Pam Haberstroh, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Jim Scott, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Shirley Garrett - choking, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Pam, Kathi, Ann 15 & 10 year pens, 1986 June 2 (Box 9)
  - Dunn Loring Metro Opening, 1986 June 7 (Box 9)
  - Lord Fairfax (Nicholas Fairfax), 1986 June 11 (Box 9)
  - Lillian Bailey, 1986 June 30 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Junior Miss - Lori Joe Smith, 1986 June 30 (Box 9)
  - Shouse Award Outstanding Violinist - Julie Kean, 1986 June 30 (Box 9)
  - NACo Awards, 1986 July 21 (Box 9)
  - University View Child Care, 1986 July 28 (Box 9)
  - Jana Graves - Mondloch House, 1986 July 28 (Box 9)
  - Good News Jail and Prison Ministries, 1986 August 4 (Box 9)
  - Dunn Loring Centennial, 1986 August 4 (Box 9)
  - West Springfield Softball Team, 1986 August 4 (Box 9)
  - Dulles Ramp Opening, 1986 August 4 (Box 9)
  - United Way Month, 1986 September 8 (Box 9)
  - Constitution Week, 1986 September 8 (Box 9)
  - Giant & J.C. Penney's, 1986 September 8 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Connector bus anniversary, 1986 September 29 (Box 9)
  - David Gehr, NOVA District Engineer for VDH&T (retiring), 1986 September 29 (Box 9)
  - Hunger Awareness Week, 1986 September 29 (Box 9)
  - Dunn Loring Centennial celebration organizers, 1986 September 29 (Box 9)
  - Fire Prevention Week, 1986 October 6 (Box 9)
  - Herndon-Reston Adult Softball Council, 1986 October 6 (Box 9)
  - Head Start Program - Balloon Launch, 1986 October (Box 9)
  - Burke Centre Park and Ride Lot Dedication Ceremony, 1986 October 25 (Box 9)
  - Fairfax Symphony Month, 1986 October 27 (Box 9)
  - Write-A-Thon Day, 1986 October 27 (Box 9)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week, 1986 October 27 (Box 9)
  - Exceptional Design Awards Media Tour (PRC, Ramada Renaissance, VA Power, Church, Meadowlark), 1986 November 14 (Box 9)
  - FCCA - National Arts Week, 1986 November 17 (Box 9)
  - Woodson High School Band, 1986 November 17 (Box 9)
  - Exceptional Design Awards, 1986 November 17 (Box 9)
  - Resolution for Soviet Jews, 1986 November 17 (Box 9)
  - Springfield Central Business District - Veterans Bridge Dedication Ceremony (aerials), 1986 November 22 (Box 9)
  - Food for Christmas Drive, 1986 November 24 (Box 9)
  - James F. Wild (Chairman FCPA), 1986 November 24 (Box 9)
  - Special Achievement Awards (Comm. For Disabled Persons), 1986 November 24 (Box 9)
  - Reston/North County Community Shelter Groundbreaking, 1986 November 25 (Box 9)
  - Mount Vernon Shelter Dedication, 1986 December 6 (Box 9)
  - FCCA, 1986 December 8 (Box 9)
  - Wallace Burton (county employee), 1986 December 8 (Box 9)
  - Child Care groups, 1986 December 8 (Box 9)
  - Edison High School Football Team, 1986 December 15 (Box 9)
  - Les Dorson Awards, 1986 December 15 (Box 9)
- Series 6: Photo and Negative File, 1987-2006
  - Youth Coaches, 1987 January 12 (Box 10)
  - Clinic Volunteers and Mr. Hoft, 1987 January 12 (Box 10)
  - Children's Dental Health Month, 1987 January 16 (Box 10)
  - Elizabeth Brinton, 1987 February 9 (Box 10)
  - Mail Room Staff, 1987 February 28 (Box 10)
  - Lee Holt and Robin Vogel, 1987 February 23 (Box 10)
  - Save Your Vision Week, 1987 February 25 (Box 10)
  - Parenting Day, 1987 March 9 (Box 10)
  - John Clayton, 1987 March 9 (Box 10)
  - Child Care Award Winners, 1987 March 16 (Box 10)
  - A. Lammond, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - Bill Hudson, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - Kovar Tootsie Roll Weekend, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - Julie Chickenburger, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - Budget Award, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - Flint Hill, 1987 March 23 (Box 10)
  - JEB Stuart girls basketball team, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Corp Volunteer Council, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Prof. Secretary Week, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Volunteer Week, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - World Health Day, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Child Care Award Winners, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Professional of the Year Awards, 1987 April 6 (Box 10)
  - Child Abuse Prevention Month, 1987 April 7 (Box 10)
  - National Education for Business Wek, 1987 April 7 (Box 10)
  - Foreign officials County Executive office, 1987 April 16 (Box 10)
  - FFCCSB Volunteer Week, 1987 April 24 (Box 10)
  - Arbor Day Ceremony, 1987 April 27 (Box 10)
  - Springfield Chamber of Commerce and Civic Association, 1987 April 27 (Box 10)
  - Teacher's Appreciation Week, 1987 April 27 (Box 10)
  - Victims Rights Week, 1987 April 27 (Box 10)
  - Jon Strother, 1987 April 27 (Box 10)
  - Barrier Awareness Day, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Older Americans Month, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Historic Preservation Week, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Fairfax Fair Week, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Rosemary Annuziatta, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Household Hazardous Wastes Awareness Month, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Mental Health Month, 1987 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Tax Lines, 1987 May (Box 10)
  - Tourism Week, 1987 May 18 (Box 10)
  - Erin Keogh, 1987 May 18 (Box 10)
  - EQAC certificates/appointment of students to EQAC, 1987 May 18 (Box 10)
  - Safe Boating Month, 1987 May 18 (Box 10)
  - Savings Bonds Campaign, 1987 May 18 (Box 10)
  - Small Business Week, 1987 June 1 (Box 10)
  - Bicentennial of the Constitution, 1987 June 1 (Box 10)
  - Junior League of the Northern Virginia and D.C., 1987 June 1 (Box 10)
  - Troa, Mt. Vernon Chapter, 1987 June 15 (Box 10)
  - Van Volunteers, 1987 June 15 (Box 10)
  - Onthank Awards, 1987 June 15 (Box 10)
  - Senior Olympians, 1987 June 15 (Box 10)
  - Physical Therapy Week, 1987 June 22 (Box 10)
  - Hewitt Crosby (EQAC), 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Marcus Williams, 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - South High School Parents and Teachers, 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Salvation Army, 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Red Cross, 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Langley High School Boys tennis team, 1987 June 29 (Box 10)
  - Ribbon Cutting County Newspaper Recycling Program, 1987 July 1 (Box 10)
  - Government Center Model and Pictures, 1987 July 6 (Box 10)
  - NACO, 1987 July 20 (Box 10)
  - Special Olympians, 1987 July 20 (Box 10)
  - Eddie Yellman, 1987 July 20 (Box 10)
  - Silver Haired Legislature, 1987 July 27 (Box 10)
  - Claude Moore Colonial Farm, 1987 July 27 (Box 10)
  - Northern Virginia Hawks Basketball Team, 1987 August 3 (Box 10)
  - Gum Springs Community, 1987 August 3 (Box 10)
  - EDNA Marie Middleton, 1987 August 3 (Box 10)
  - WM Goodell, 1987 August 3 (Box 10)
  - Award for Mrs. Pennino from NVYSC, 1987 August 3 (Box 10)
  - NACO Award Office of Transportation, 1987 August 13 (Box 10)
  - Human Services Building, 1987 September 11 (Box 10)
  - Dr. Claude Moore, 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - Down Syndrome Awareness Month, 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - Mt. Vernon Band, 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - Constitution Week, 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - Deanna Consumano - VA, 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - Laura Grain (Save Life Via CPR), 1987 September 21 (Box 10)
  - North County Human Services Building Dedication, 1987 September 26 (Box 10)
  - Bailey's Crossroads Community Shelter Dedication, 1987 September 27 (Box 10)
  - Bailey's Shelter Dedication, 1987 September 30 (Box 10)
  - Giant Food, Inc., 1987 October 5 (Box 10)
  - Fire Prevention Week, 1987 October 5 (Box 10)
  - Aca Prevention and Pistol Team, 1987 October 5 (Box 10)
  - United Way Month, 1987 October 5 (Box 10)
  - EPA ceremony Lower Potomac Plant, 1987 October 6 (Box 10)
  - Financial Education Week, 1987 October 12 (Box 10)
  - B'nai B'rith Week, 1987 October 16 (Box 10)
  - Signing Ceremony with Sallaudet University, 1987 October 19 (Box 10)
  - Substance Abuse Awareness Week, 1987 October 29 (Box 10)
  - FCCA Arts Week, 1987 October 29 (Box 10)
  - Domestic Violence Awareness, 1987 October 29 (Box 10)
  - Master H. Klee and Spanish Tae Kwon, 1987 November 20 (Box 10)
  - Run to Daylight Organization, 1987 November 23 (Box 10)
  - Exceptional Design Awards, 1987 November 23 (Box 10)
  - Food for All seasoned Drive, 1987 November 30 (Box 10)
  - Special achievement Awards Ceremony for disabled people, 1987 November 30 (Box 10)
  - Reston Homeless Shelter ceremony, 1987 December 5 (Box 10)
  - Marci Brunson, 1987 December 7 (Box 10)
  - Lee Rucker, 1987 December 14 (Box 10)
  - BOS and J. together, 1987 December 14 (Box 10)
  - Patricia Smith (of PANPAA), 1988 January 11 (Box 10)
  - Venezuela Visitors, 1988 January 20-21 (Box 10)
  - Handicapped Courageous Award to Montgomery County Stroke Club, 1988 January 20 (Box 10)
  - Catherine Simmons reitred from county after 30 years, 1988 January 25 (Box 10)
  - Evergreen Friendship Club, 1988 February 8 (Box 10)
  - Save Your Vision Week, 1988 February 9 (Box 10)
  - Engineers and Architects Day, 1988 February 22 (Box 10)
  - Big Bros. Proc, 1988 February 23 (Box 10)
  - Parenting Day, 1988 February 29 (Box 10)
  - Women's History Month, 1988 February 29 (Box 10)
  - American Association of University Women Pres., 1988 March 3 (Box 10)
  - Certificates for 2 volunteers with F.E.C., 1988 March 7 (Box 10)
  - Government Center shots, 1988 March 9 (Box 10)
  - National Symphony on Orchestra's Association, 1988 March 14 (Box 10)
  - Stop Child Abuse Now (SCAN), 1988 March 21 (Box 10)
  - James Wild (FCPA-retiring), 1988 March 28 (Box 10)
  - Transportation Safety Commission, 1988 March 28 (Box 10)
  - Stan Hutcheson, 1988 March 28 (Box 10)
  - Keep Fairfax County Beautiful Month, 1988 March 28 (Box 10)
  - Savings Bond Campaign 1988, 1988 March 28 (Box 10)
  - Child Care Professional of the Year Award, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - League of Women Voters 40th Anniversary, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Organ and Tissue Donor Awareness Week, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Family Day Care Provider Week, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Kovar Tootsie Roll Weekend, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Week of the Young Child, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - George Snyder, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - 1988 Suggestion Ceremony Awards, 1988 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Volunteer Week, 1988 April 15 (Box 10)
  - Verdia's 40th Birthday, 1988 April (Box 10)
  - Yvonne's and Lilly's outstanding performance awards, 1988 April 22 (Box 10)
  - Arbor Day photos, 1988 April 25 (Box 10)
  - Public Works Week, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Older Americans Month, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - 4-H Ambassadors Club, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Household Hazardous Waste Awareness, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Mt. Vernon High School Basketball team and coach, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Report of Citizens Task Force in the Spring 1988 Bond Referendum, 1988 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Transfax 88 Reception, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Small Business Week, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Older Americans Month, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Mt. Vernon High School Ban, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Barbara Alexander retiree, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Mental Health Week, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Historic Preservation Week, 1988 May 9 (Box 10)
  - Firefighters, 1988 May 17 (Box 10)
  - Government finance officers award, 1988 May 23 (Box 10)
  - Hohn Catellani (RHA), 1988 May 23 (Box 10)
  - Barbara Hildreth (NVRPA), 1988 May 23 (Box 10)
  - Safe Beating Month, 1988 May 23 (Box 10)
  - West Potomac High School Band, 1988 May 23 (Box 10)
  - Ray Brooks (retiring from Commission on Aging), 1988 June 6 (Box 10)
  - VA Wrestling Team, 1988 June 6 (Box 10)
  - David Bozien, 1988 June 20 (Box 10)
  - Thomas McCarn(?) retiring President of Groveton Civic Association, 1988 June 20 (Box 10)
  - Students who received scholarships MADD, 1988 July 11 (Box 10)
  - Reception for Fairfax Fair contribution, 1988 July 15 (Box 10)
  - Shots of J at work, 1988 July 15 (Box 10)
  - Jail/PRISM Month, 1988 July 15 (Box 10)
  - Josephine Senecal, 1988 July 25 (Box 10)
  - Kaiser Permanente 12 officials from First Virginia Bank who helped with the Medical Care for Children, 1988 July 25 (Box 10)
  - Mary Collier, 1988 August 1 (Box 10)
  - Smith Commission, 1988 August 1 (Box 10)
  - Lifeguards, 1988 August 1 (Box 10)
  - Freddie Mac playground dedication - North County Community Shelter, 1988 August 3 (Box 10)
  - Joanne Field - School Board appointment, 1988 September 26 (Box 10)
  - United Way, 1988 September 26 (Box 10)
  - Mental Illness Awareness, 1988 September 26 (Box 10)
  - NACO Award Winners, 1988 October (Box 10)
  - Henry (?), 1988 October 31 (Box 10)
  - Art Week, 1988 October 31 (Box 10)
  - Flakne, 1988 October 31 (Box 10)
  - Bond Task Force 1988, 1988 November 28 (Box 10)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 1988 November 28 (Box 10)
  - Jo Ann Ferguson, 1988 November 28 (Box 10)
  - Vienna/Falls Church, 1988 November 28 (Box 10)
  - Volunteer Fire Department Awards, 1988 December 5 (Box 10)
  - Burke History Book, 1988 December 5 (Box 10)
  - Council of the Arts, 1989 January 23 (Box 10)
  - EQAS - Environmental Report, 1989 January 23 (Box 10)
  - Library Anniversary, 1989 January 30 (Box 10)
  - John Thillman resigned from Planning Commission, 1989 January 30 (Box 10)
  - Planning Commission Swears In, 1989 February 1 (Box 10)
  - Boy Scouts, 1989 February 13 (Box 10)
  - Engineer Day, 1989 February 13 (Box 10)
  - C.J. Cooper (Big Brother), 1989 February 13 (Box 10)
  - Florence Townsend, 1989 February 27 (Box 10)
  - Venezuelans, 1989 March 1 (Box 10)
  - NACIO Awards, 1989 March 17 (Box 10)
  - Alexander's Resolution from VA, 1989 March 17 (Box 10)
  - Wheelchair Race, 1989 March 17 (Box 10)
  - Drug Awareness Week, 1989 March 17 (Box 10)
  - Tootsie Roll, 1989 March 20 (Box 10)
  - Police (Dellore, Dawson), 1989 March 20 (Box 10)
  - Keep Fairfax County Beautiful, 1989 March 20 (Box 10)
  - De Moley, 1989 March 20 (Box 10)
  - Organ Donor Awareness Week, 1989 March 30 (Box 10)
  - Planning Commission Swear In, 1989 April 6 (Box 10)
  - VA. Adult Abuse, 1989 April 18 (Box 10)